List<Map<String, dynamic>> oRPartOneQuestions = [
  {
    'question':
    'Which surgical instrument is used for grasping and holding tissues during a procedure?',
    'answers': ['Hemostat.', 'Trocar.', 'Retractor.', 'Suture needle',],
    'correctIndex': 0,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'What does the primary purpose of a Mayo stand in the operating room?',
    'answers': [
      'To hold sterile instruments.',
      'To provide lighting.',
      'To maintain patient temperature.',
      'To monitor vital signs.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 0,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'During a laparoscopic cholecystectomy, which gas is commonly used to insufflate the abdomen?',
    'answers': ['Oxygen.', 'Nitrous oxide.', 'Carbon dioxide.', 'Helium.',],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'Which surgical procedure involves the removal of the entire colon and rectum?',
    'answers': [
      'Appendectomy.',
      'Cholecystectomy.',
      'Colectomy.',
      'Nephrectomy.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'What type of incision is made vertically along the midline of the abdomen for many abdominal surgeries?',
    'answers': [
      'Transverse incision.',
      'Pfannenstiel incision.',
      'Midline incision.',
      'Paramedian incision.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'Which of the following is a commonly used non-absorbable suture material?',
    'answers': ['Polyglactin.', 'Silk.', 'Polydioxanone.', 'Catgut.',],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'During open-heart surgery, what type of pump is used to temporarily take over the function of the heart and lungs?',
    'answers': [
      'Hemodialysis machine.',
      'Cardiopulmonary bypass machine.',
      'Ventilator.',
      'Echocardiogram machine.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'Which surgical specialty focuses on the treatment of musculoskeletal system disorders?',
    'answers': [
      'Neurosurgery.',
      'Orthopedic surgery.',
      'Cardiothoracic surgery.',
      'Plastic surgery.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'In a sterile field, what is the primary function of a surgical drape?',
    'answers': [
      'Maintain temperature.',
      'Prevent contamination.',
      'Illuminate the surgical site.',
      'Provide traction.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'Which surgical instrument is commonly used to cut bone during orthopedic procedures?',
    'answers': ['Scissors.', 'Rongeur.', 'Hemostat.', 'Trocar.',],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'What term describes the removal of a segment of a blood vessel and its subsequent repair?',
    'answers': ['Anastomosis.', 'Ligation.', 'Resection.', 'Clipping.',],
    'correctIndex': 0,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'During a cesarean section, which layer of the abdominal wall is incised first?',
    'answers': ['Peritoneum.', 'Fascia.', 'Muscles.', 'Skin.',],
    'correctIndex': 3,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'Which of the following is NOT a type of surgical site infection (SSI)?',
    'answers': [
      'Superficial SSI.',
      'Deep incisional SSI.',
      'Organ-space SSI.',
      'Extraneous SSI.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 3,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'What is the purpose of a "time-out" procedure in the operating room?',
    'answers': [
      'To update the patient\'s family on progress.',
      'To take a break during surgery.',
      'To verify patient identity, procedure, and surgical site.',
      'To discuss postoperative care plans.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'In laparoscopic surgery, what is the term for the initial insertion point for trocars and instruments?',
    'answers': [
      'Port site.',
      'Incision site.',
      'Trocar site.',
      'Veress needle site.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'Which type of anesthesia involves numbing a specific region of the body, often used in minor surgical procedures?',
    'answers': [
      'General anesthesia.',
      'Epidural anesthesia.',
      'Local anesthesia.',
      'Spinal anesthesia.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'During a craniotomy, what type of instrument is used to remove bone from the skull?',
    'answers': ['Gouge.', 'Rongeur.', 'Curette.', 'Osteotome.',],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'Which surgical procedure is performed to remove an inflamed or infected appendix?',
    'answers': [
      'Appendectomy.',
      'Cholecystectomy.',
      'Colectomy.',
      'Gastrectomy.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 0,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'What term describes the process of sealing blood vessels or tissue using extreme cold?',
    'answers': [
      'Cauterization.',
      'Cryosurgery.',
      'Electrocautery.',
      'Laser surgery.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'During cardiac bypass surgery, what is the purpose of using the heart-lung machine?',
    'answers': [
      'To maintain oxygen supply to the brain.',
      'To completely replace the patient\'s heart.',
      'To divert blood away from the heart temporarily.',
      'To monitor blood pressure during surgery.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'What surgical instrument is commonly used to cut through thick tissue or bone?',
    'answers': ['Scissors.', 'Hemostat.', 'Scalpel.', 'Mayo scissors.',],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'During a craniotomy, what is the term for the removal of a circular section of bone from the skull?',
    'answers': ['Trephination.', 'Perforation.', 'Incision.', 'Resection.',],
    'correctIndex': 0,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'Which type of electrosurgical instrument used to cut tissue by rapidly heating it?',
    'answers': [
      'Cautery pen.',
      'Harmonic scalpel.',
      'Laser scalpel.',
      'Cryoprobe.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'What is the primary role of a surgical technologist in the operating room?',
    'answers': [
      'Administering anesthesia.',
      'Assisting the surgeon during the procedure.',
      'Monitoring vital signs.',
      'Sterilizing instruments.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'In a laparoscopic cholecystectomy, what is the purpose of the Veress needle?',
    'answers': [
      'To inject contrast dye.',
      'To create a pneumoperitoneum.',
      'To aspirate fluids.',
      'To cut tissue.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'Which type of suture material is absorbable and often used for internal tissue layers?',
    'answers': ['Silk.', 'Nylon.', 'Vicryl.', 'Prolene.',],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'During an abdominal surgery, what is the primary function of wound retractors?',
    'answers': [
      'Hemostasis.',
      'Tissue dissection.',
      'Exposure and visualization.',
      'Infection prevention.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'Which of the following is a common complication of laparoscopic surgery involving the abdominal cavity?',
    'answers': ['Air embolism.', 'Cardiac arrest.', 'Hyperthermia.', 'Stroke.',],
    'correctIndex': 0,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'What is the term for the process of removing excess fluid and blood from the surgical field during an operation?',
    'answers': ['Aspiration.', 'Lavage.', 'Irrigation.', 'Hemostasis.',],
    'correctIndex': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
    'What surgical instrument is used to grasp and remove foreign bodies or tissue, such as tumors?',
    'answers': [
      'Allis forceps.',
      'Mosquito forceps.',
      'Adson forceps.',
      'Hemostats.',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 0,
  },
];
